(Lucy:)Can I tell you something?
(Lucy:)I was so nervous about seeing you...
(Lucy:)...before I left my apartment, I put roll-on
antiperspirant all over my body.
- Really?
- Yeah.
(Lucy:)If sweat starts squirting out
the top of my head, you'll know why.
(Raj:)I'm sorry to put you through that.
It's okay. I'm trying to force myself
to do things that make me scared.
(Raj:)What else have you been
thinking about doing?
(Lucy:)Well, let's see.
(Lucy:)I'd love to be able to tell the lady
who cuts my hair that I don't like bangs.
- I like your bangs.
- Thanks, I like them too.
- What else?
- Hmm.
It's a tie between sending food back
in a restaurant...
...and saying no to kids
who sell magazines door to door.
(Raj:)Those are both toughies.
(Lucy:)I know. I have a two-year subscription
to Guns and Ammo.